

Caleb **Regan**

Front-End Web Developer

 3340 Nancy Drive, Auburn, California

☑ calebregann@gmail.com

% +1 818-519-7378

EDUCATION

Cybersecurity

Purdue University Global 2023 - Present

Neuroscience

University of Colorado Boulder 2020 - 2022

SKILLS

Skills & Experience

Front-End Development

Information Security Data Analysis

Responsive Design Code Review

API Integration Collaboration

Problem Solving Cloud Services

Automation Scripting

Network Security DevOps Practices

Database Management

TECHNOLOGIES

Known Coding Languages & Softwares

Python SQL Azure JavaScript

React Docker Linux Systems

HTML CSS Node.js Git

HOBBIES

- Music
- Programming
- Video Games
- Exercise

LANGUAGES

• English

Professional Summary

Front-End Web Developer with experience creating user-friendly interfaces that boost engagement and satisfaction. Excels in team collaboration, utilizing responsive design and JavaScript frameworks to enhance performance and user experience. Adept at troubleshooting and resolving front-end issues, contributing to increased website traffic and user retention. Experienced in automating processes with Python as well as storing and manipulating data with SQL. Proficient with Docker and Azure; familiar with Kubernetes and AWS.

Experience

Front-End Web Developer

Complex Carbon Co.

Remote

Aug 2023 - Present

- > Developed user-friendly interfaces enhancing user engagement and satisfaction.
- > Collaborated with design teams to implement responsive and accessible web solutions.
- > Utilized JavaScript frameworks to optimize page load times and performance.
- > Experience troubleshooting and resolving front-end issues ensuring seamless user experience.
- > Produces measurable improvements in website traffic and user retention.

Relevant Courses

Cybersecurity

Purdue University Global

2023 - Present

Completed Courses

- > IT104 Introduction to Cybersecurity
- > IT273 Networking Concepts
- > IN203 Networking With Microsoft Technologies
- > IT286 Network Security Concepts
- > MM212 College Algebra
- > MM250 Discrete Mathematics
- > IT275 Linux System Administration
- > IT244 Python Programming

Courses In Progress

- > IN205 Routing and Switching I
- > IN206 Routing and Switching II
- > IT262 Certified Ethical Hacking I

Certificates

Google Cybersecurity

Coursera

Jun 2023 - Oct 2023

References

Stephen Falsetti

Complex Carbon Co, Owner

% +1 650-862-8380

Mike Gardner

Rocky Mountain Home Preservation, Owner

oxdim jmgardner@gmail.com

% +1 650-283-6392